Local 1199 Additional Records 5651
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Statistics, Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Supermarkets, General (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Survey of Minority Groups on 1199 Stores, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Temporary Non-Association Agreements - Samples (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Booklet (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Twenty Five Year Member's Club, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Wage and Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Files - A - Z (through 1976) (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations - A-C-74, 1975-1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations - Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Arbitrations - Modification Agreement, Changes in Procedure-71, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Chain Stores Lists-70, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Cohen, Abraham - Case-68, 1962-1968 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Contract Advisory Committee-73, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Contract Negotiations, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Cosmopolitan Research and Medical Laboratories-73, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Decision - Case F.G. U9-65 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Employers Groups - Alphabetically: (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Central Flushing Medical Group, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Jamaica Medical Group: Arbitrations (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Jamaica Medical Group: Contracts and Memos of Agreement (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Jamaica Medical Group - General (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Jamaica Medical Group - Lockout, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Jamaica Medical Group - Negotiations-71, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Jamaica Medical Group - Organization (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Jamaica Medical Group - Strike, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Jamaica Medical Group - VanWyck Center Removal (Box 37, Folder 10)
- King's Highway Medical Group, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- LaGuardia Medical Group-70, 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- New York City Medical Group-73, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- New York City Society of Hospital Pharmacists, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- St. Mark's Doctor's Group (Box 38, Folder 1)
- St. Mark's Doctor's Group - Supplemental Agreement, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- United Pharmacists Guild, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Upper Manhattan Medical Group-71, 1967-1971 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Upper Manhattan Medical Group - Salters (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Upper Queens Medical Group, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Yorkville Medical Group, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- NLRB- Listed Alphabetically: (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Baratta's Pharmacy, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Bernstein Drugs, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Dale Drugs, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Doctor's Offices Medical Group, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- East Nassau Medical Group, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Eastman Pick & Save Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Economy Drug Store, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Ehrenberg's Pharmacy, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Jamie Ferguson, Inc., I965, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Gilman Pharmacy, Inc., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Glenwood Pharmacy, I963, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Globe Canteen, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Gramercy Pharmacy, Inc., I963, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Gregorius Pharmacy, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Hudson Vitamin Products, Inc., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Jamaica Medical Group, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Jarius Surgical Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Kopper Drug Corp., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Kew Gardens General Hospital, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- King's County Research Labs., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- King's Highway Hospital, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Kingston Drug, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Klipp's Pharmacy, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Ko-Ed Cater's Inc., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- L&F Drug Corp., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Landau Pharmacy, I96U, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Lefrak City Pharmacy, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Lichtenstein Pharmacy, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Lowes Smithtown Drug, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Lynette Drugs, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Man's Drug Co., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Marrud, Inc., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Litt Martin Value Centers, Inc., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Massapequa Park Drug, Inc., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- J.H. Miller Pharmacy, Inc., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Miller Pharmacy, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Mintzes, Inc., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Morblock Foods, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Mount Morris Pharmacy, Inc., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Nathaniel Golden, Inc., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Peller & Silverman Pharmacy, I969, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- Perla Pharmacy, Inc., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Royal Nassau Drug Corp., 1961 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- St. James Drug, Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 52)
- Sam's Wholesale Sundries, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 53)
- Schein, Henry, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 54)
- Shopping Town Drug Corp, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 55)
- Semco International, Inc., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 56)
- Shally Pharmacy, Inc., 1957 (Box 38, Folder 57)
- Sharon Drug, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 58)
- Shears Pharmacy, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 59)
- Silver Rite Drugs, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 60)
- Smith Ethical Pharmacy, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 61)
- Sound View Station Drug Store, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 62)
- Super X Drugs of NY Inc., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 63)
- Thriftway Drug Corp., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 64)
- Tower Drugs, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 65)
- Towne Pharmacy, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 66)
- Tunick Pharmacy, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 67)
- Vito safe Pharmacy, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 68)
- Whelan Drug Stores Co., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 69)
- Whitaker Pharmacy, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 70)
- Wili-Deb Distributor's Inc., 1965 (Box 38, Folder 71)
- Wood Island Pharmacy, Inc., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 72)
- Wyandanch Pharmacy, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 73)
- Wyckoff Heights Hospital, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 74)
- Negotiations - Drug Industry, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 75)
- NYSLRB - Lenux Hill Hospital, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 76)
- NYSLRB - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 77)
- NYSLRB - Nassau Hospital Assn, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 78)
- NYSLRB - Pro-Servicing Corp., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 79)
- NYSLRB - Univ. Hospital of NYU Medical Center (Box 38, Folder 80)
- Notice of Expiration of Contract, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 81)
- Organization - Collective Bargaining, 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 82)
- Retail Food Clerk's Union, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 83)
- Steinberg (Box 38, Folder 84)
- Stores- Alphabetically: (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Chatterbox Coffee Shop, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Dwight Coffee shop, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- El-Nor Medical Supply & Pharmacy, Inc., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Genovesse's Drug Store - Strike, I969, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Haven Chemists, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Hillsborough Classroom Teachers Assn., 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Health and Hospital Corp., 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Honig's Dept. Store, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Hudson National, 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Jalar Cosmetics (Police Investigation of Pickets) (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Jamron Drug, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- King's County Research Labs, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 13)
- King's County Research Lab Strike, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- LaGuardia Hospital, I969-7O, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- L.I. Laboratories, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Manhasset Medical Center Pharmacy, Inc., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- L.H. Martin Discount Stores, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Masters, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Metropolitan-Hudson, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Montefiore Coffee Shop, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Parkway Hospital Arbitration, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Perfect Photo, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Royal Drug Store vs. Matthew Peliksson, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Six Hundred and Sixty-Six Cosmetics, Inc., 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Wychoff Heights Hospital, 1967-1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Stores Dropped, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Stores New, 1971-1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Contract Files (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Dropped Contracts, A-L (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Dropped Contracts, L-Z (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Expired Contracts, A-0, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Expired Contracts, P-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Expired Contracts, A-E, 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Expired Contracts, E-K, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations, A-I, 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Arbitrations, J-W, 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Bronx, 1974-1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn, 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Community Hospital - Brooklyn, 1976-1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- League of Voluntary Hospitals, 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Manhattan East, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Manhattan West, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- NLRB Certifications, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Queens, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Connecticut Files (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Colchester Convalescent Home (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Community Health Services, Inc. Hartford (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Connecticut Area - General (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Contracts (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Danbury Health Co. (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Golden Manor (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Greenwood Convalescent Home (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Healthcare Housekeeping Systems, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Highland Acres Extend-a-care Center (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Hilldale Convalescent Home (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Jewish Home for Aged, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Meadows Convalescent Home (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Mountain Laurel Healthcare (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Mount Sinai Hospital - Connecticut (Box 50, Folder 3)
- New Fairview Convalescent Home (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Pond Point Nursing Home (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Prospect Nursing & Convalescent Center, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Reliable Food Services Co., Inc. (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Ridge Hill Convalescent Home (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Ridgewood Central Health Center (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Roncalli Health Center (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Royal Crest Convalescent Home (Box 50, Folder 11)
- St. Mary's Home (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Seaside Convalescent Hospital, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Stula's Convalescent Hospital, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 14)
- University of Bridgeport (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Waterbury Hospital (Box 50, Folder 16)
- West Haven Manor Nursing Home (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Westport Manor Convalescent Center, Inc. (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Wyndover Convalescent Hospital (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Executive Files (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Annual Reports of Legal Services, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Benefit Fund - Reports and Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Bronx-Westchester, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Comm. on Human Rights - Reports & Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Locals (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Membership Meetings, A-K, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Membership Meetings, L-Z, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Grievances, A-K (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Grievances, L-Z (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Membership Meetings, A-Z (Box 53, Folder 2)
- National Executive Board Meeting, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  May, 1977.
- National Pension Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Training and Upgrading, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Woodland, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Maimonides Hospital (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Martin Luther King Health Center (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Metropolitan Hospital (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Midtown Hospital (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Montefoire Hospital (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Morris J. Bernstein (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Mt. Sinai/Elmhurst (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Nassau Hospital (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Nassau County Contract Clinics (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Neighborhood Health Services (Box 55, Folder 11)
- New York Infirmary (Box 55, Folder 12)
- New York League for the Hard of Hearing (Box 55, Folder 13)
- New York Medical College (Box 55, Folder 14)
- New York University (Box 55, Folder 15)
- North Central Bronx/CHCC (Box 55, Folder 16)
- North Shore University Hospital (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Northside Center (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Parkway Hospital (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Peninsula General Hospital (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Public Health Research Institute (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Queens Child Guidance Center (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Queens General Hospital (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Richmond Memorial Hospital (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Rikers Island / Montefoire (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Roosevelt Hospital (Box 55, Folder 26)
- St. Barnabas Hospital (Box 55, Folder 27)
- St. John's Episcopal (Box 55, Folder 28)
- St. John's/South Shore (Box 56, Folder 1)
- St. Luke's Hospital (Box 56, Folder 2)
- St. Mary's Hospital (Box 56, Folder 3)
- St. Peter's School (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Sephardic Nursing Home (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Staten Island Hospital (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Syosset Hospital (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Trafalgar Hospital (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Unity Hospital (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Vassar Brother's (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Whitestone Hospital (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Wyckoff Heights (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Yeshiva University (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Legislative Committees thru 1977 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Legislation Correspondence thru 1977 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Mental Health (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Mental Health - Committee to Preserve (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Multiphasic Health Testing Program (Box 57, Folder 5)
- National Health Insurance (Box 57, Folder 6)
- National Health Insurance - Catastrophic Health Insurance (Box 57, Folder 7)
- National Health Insurance - Committee for (Box 57, Folder 8)
- National Health Legislation, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- National Urban League (Box 57, Folder 10)
- New York - Ad Hoc Committee Against Catastrophic Illness Insurance (Box 57, Folder 11)
- New York - State Assembly Committees (Box 58, Folder 1)
- New York - State Consumer Protection Board, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- New York State Temp. Comm. on Living Costs (Box 58, Folder 3)
- New York - Senate Committee on Health (Box 58, Folder 4)
- New York City - Health Facilities (Box 58, Folder 5)
- New York City - Health and Hospital Corp. (Box 58, Folder 6)
- New York City - Mayor's Organizational Task Force (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Planned Parenthood (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Respiratory Therapy (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Vouchers through 1978 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Abortion, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Berek, Judy, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Carnegie Union Leadership Proposal (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Community Council of Greater NY, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Community Mental Health Centers Act (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Cornell University, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Day Care (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Drug Abuse (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Elections, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- General Prof. Comm., I976, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Health Professionals - New Health Assn. for (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Health Professionals for Political Action (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Health Statistics (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Health Statistics (National Center for) (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Labor Statistics (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Legislative Program, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Medical Committee for Human Rights (Box 59, Folder 9)
- New York Urban Coalition - Health Task Force (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Physicians (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Prisons (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Regional Advisory Group (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Sickle-Cell Anemia (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Visitors (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Aging and Elderly, 1971-1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Statements and Resolutions, 1971-1975 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO, NYC-CLC, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO, NYC-CLC, Hospital and Medical Care, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Blue-Cross/Blue-Shield (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Congressional Visits, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Consumer Assembly, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Consumer Groups (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Cornell, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Cornell - School of ILR, 1972-1975 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Correspondence - Judy Berek, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Other, 1973-1975 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Elections 1199, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Elections-Endorsements, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Elections and Voter Registration, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Federal Register (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Health Care - USA (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Hearing - Testimony, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Legislative Correspondence, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Legislative Representatives for Social Concern (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Legislative Reporter, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- League of Women Voter's, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Lobbying (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Nixon Budget Cuts (Box 61, Folder 14)
- NYS Legislative Budget - Rockefeller (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Regional Medical Program, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Regional Medical Program Grant Application, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Training & Upgrading Fund, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Voter Registration (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Vouchers - Organizations and General Services, Admin., 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Vouchers Subscriptions (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Berek, Judy - President, CLUW (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Committee and Attendance Lists (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Conferences (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 25)
- 1199 - DLUW (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Hearings (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Minutes - Resolutions (Box 63, Folder 1)
- NYC-CLUW Actions (Box 63, Folder 2)
- NYC-CLUW Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 3)
- NYC-CLUW Meeting Notices (Box 63, Folder 4)
- NYC-CLUW Reports (Box 63, Folder 5)
- New York Trade Union Women (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Other Chapters (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Reports (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Steering Committee (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Trade Union Women Studies (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Delegate Newsletters, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- 1199 News, 1975-1979 (Box 64, Folder 2)